We paint the faces, we choose the dress To hide
the pices of the emptiness We walk the avenue in
borrowed clothes And play the part everybody
knows A gallery of ghosts inside the hall
We smile to prove we haven't lost our Welcome to
the masquerade In the fragile dress we have made
Spinning in the shadows out of sight Stanking on
the edges of the knife In the masquerade
The music swelters and the voices rise To drown
the secrets in our weary eyes We hold together
when the curtain falls No one answers when the
echo calls A beautiful illusion we protect
A grand design of cause and of effect Welcome to
the masquerade In the fragile fortress we have
made Spinning the shadows out of sight Danking
on the edges of the night In the masquerade
Take off the mask, the hour is late We cannot
always hide from fate The cold hours bleed, the
mirrors crack And there is no way turning back
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Welcome to the masquerade In the fragile
fortress we have made Spinning in the shadows
out of sight Standing on the edges of the night In
the masquerade
The painted smiles The fading spark